Baby,ba-ba di ba.....baby!
爸爸?
Dad!?
迈克，你保证过一定要好好准备
Mike,you promised me you'd be studying
演讲课的功课！
for your speech class exam.
我要准备。
I am!
你得重新开始！
Well,start over!
我带着耳机他怎么知道？！
I don't get it,I was wearing headphones.
温课了，Mike！
Study Mike!
好
Alright!
喂
Hello.
HI，波拿老兄你好吗？
Hey Boner,my man! How are you doing?
呃，我可以用上温课的间隙时间。
Yeah,I could use a study break.
呃，对对，游戏厅很好玩。
Oh,yeah,yeah,the Arcade sounds great.
等等，我破产了。
Oh wait a second,I'm broke.
我想你可以先借我。。
You think you could lend me like...
好的，好的，我把新账旧账一起还你。
alright,alright,alright; I'll pay you back for that,
别挂断。
and for this,ok? Oh,hold on a second.
Oh Carol!
Carol？
一分钱也别想
Not a Dime.
波拿，恐怕我。。OH，你等一下。
Bone,I don't know,oh may....oh hold on a minute.
好弟弟BEN！
Oh Benny my man!
没门，Mike！
Not a chance Mike!
波拿，恐怕我还需要一点时间。
Listen Bone,er...this could take a couple of seconds.
好，你别走开。
You wanna hold? Ok,don't go away.
没关系，我等着你。
No problem. I'll wait right here.
Ben，我亲爱的小兄弟。
Ben! My little compadre!!
哦？
Ha??
Ben，你这么怀疑地看着我，
Ben,you know when you look at me suspiciously like that
太使我伤心了。
it hurts.
很好。
Good.
Ben，听着，既然咱们是兄弟
Ben,come on! I mean we're brothers,you know.
就应该同心协力，一眨眼
This is our time to bond. And you know,before you know it,
你就是大人了。
you'll be a grown man and...
你就要蹲监狱了！
You'll be in prison.
那好吧，如果你不想看
Alright,ok,fine,if you don't want to see
我这套新的扑克游戏就不找你了。
this great new card trick that I learnt,
你本来可以用它从你的朋友那赢一大笔钱的。
that you could use to win big money out of your trusting little friends...
要多少钱？
How much money?
很多！
Plenty?
你把牌拿来。
Get the cards.
爸爸好象说过再也不允许
I thought Dad said you weren't supposed to
你和Ben玩扑克牌了。
be playing cards with Ben anymore.
我们在加强感情！
Hey! We're bonding!
好吧。你任意抽一张，我能告诉你是什么牌。
Ok. Now pick a card any card,and I'll tell you what it is.
我可以押一美元。
And I'll bet...even I'll say a Dollar on it.
好吧，好吧你不用押一美元，
Ok,alright,you don't have to bet a dollar,
你用虚拟的一美元。
just make it a pretend Dollar.
这是黑桃皇后。
It's the Queen of Spades.
这是方块七！
Seven of Diamonds!
哈！
Ha!
我怎么搞糊涂了。
Gosh! Why did I mess up?
好，再来试试。
Alright here,let me try it again.
是红心ACE？
The....Ace of Hearts?
是方块九。
Nine of Diamonds!
你已经输了两美元了。
You owe him two Dollars.
又不是来真的。为什么不灵了呢？
Pretend Dollars! Guys why isn't this working?
我来押月规钱，
I bet my allowance.
一共四美元。这可是真的钱。
Four Dollars. Real Dollars.
听着Ben，
You know Ben,
你就这样占我的便宜也太恶心了！
it's real sleazy of you to take advantage of me like this.
我押上五美元。
Five Dollars more.
我看就算了。
Hey,come on guys!
再押一块。
And another Buck.
哦。好。
Ahhh.
这是什么？
Ok,what is it?
是方块J，我太感谢了。
Jack of Diamonds. Thank you very much.
我只有十岁，你的借口是啥？
I'm only ten. What's your excuse?
-= Subripped by Susie Shi =-       2007.08.03
喂，Mike，是你吗？
Hello Mikey,are you there?
喂？喂？！
Hello. Hello!
喂？
Hello!
Ben是你吗？
Ben,is that you?
Mike，你还在温课吗？
Mike! Are you still studying?
我在温课，爸爸。
Yo Dad,I'm on it!
吃这个。
Eat this!
Ben，你别惹我发火了。
Ben look,you're already skating on thin ice,alright.
我在游戏厅半个多小时等波拿，
I mean I just went down to the Arcade for half an hour,
是他打电话约我去的，可结果他倒没有。
after Boner calls and invites me,and he doesn't even show up!
Mike.
Mike？
波拿？
Boner?!
Mike.
Mike？
喂，听着波拿，
Hello. Boner look!
我在游戏厅等了半小时你去哪了？！
Man,I was just down at the Arcades for half an hour. Where you been?
哦，你干嘛不告诉我你在等我的回电呢！？
Oh! Why didn't you just call and tell me you were waiting on the phone?
Mike，别浪费时间了，
Mike,no wasting time!
要抓紧准备演讲课的考试。
Supposed to be working on that speech.
演讲题目选定了？
So have you settled on a topic?
未免也太早了点吧，爸爸？
Well...it's a little early Dad.
你究竟选了什么题目？
Well what are your choices?
哦，爸爸，你不是说过嘛，
Ah...Dad,Dad,you know how you...err...
你不想来逼我的嘛。
always said you never wanted to push me?
你这是在逼我。
Well,you're pushing me.
你对爸爸说你骗我们钱的事吗？
Did you tell Dad about all the money you stole from us?
什么？
What?
哦，爸爸你别听她的。
Ahh,no,no Dad she doesn't know what she's talking about.
咱俩私下说一句，我很为她担心。
Just between you and me,I'm worried about her.
你把钱都花在游戏厅了吗？
Did you spend all that money at the Arcade?
Ben这人我看他就爱乱放炮。
Ben of course has several cylinders and is firing them.
你是不是到游戏厅去玩电子游戏了？
You were down at the Arcade playing video games?
哦，这件事说起来话就长了。
That's a very complicated question Dad.
告诉我。
Try me.
我肯定没有玩什么电子游戏。
I was definitely no playing video games.
但你去了哪？
But you were there?
就呆了一小会。
For a very short time.
你是用我的钱。
With my money!
还有我的。
And mine!
那是我赢的。
I won it!
你骗的。
You stole it!
从一个小孩那里骗的!
From a little kid too!!
打赌的主意是谁出的？
Hey,whose idea was it to bet?
爸爸，我拼命劝他们别赌，
Dad look,I tried to talk 'em out of it.
我只想好好复习功课。
All I wanted to do was stay home and study.
你竟会骗家里人的钱?!
So you conned your own family out of money?
这种听起来也太刺耳了。
Well,I wouldn't put it exactly that way.
得了，mike
Come on Mike!
可是你几时才能了解骗人最终会害自己？
When are you gonna learn that conning people will only hurt you?
哦……
Oh please.
听着Mike，我在说你的前途。
No,Mike,I'm talking about your future here!
骗子的下场十有八九
You know that nine out of ten con-men end up
只能靠按摩过日子。
spending empty bitter lives as chiropractors?
我希望你能找一个比那些专治腰伤的人
Mike,I want something better for you than
再好一点的工作。
a life of hugging men who've thrown their backs out.
好了，我选的题目是不雅的暴露。
Ok. My topic is "indecent exposure".
有趣的是世界上某些地方，
Now,it's interesting to note,that in some places in the world,
法律规定他们掩盖的唯一地方是
the only part of a female body that,by law,
女性的脸。
must be covered is the face.
只要你去过化妆品商店
And if you've been to a Convenience store lately,
就能体会到这法律是从哪来的了。
you can clearly see where that law comes from! Naaa.
妈妈你怎么这么早就回来了？
Hey Mom,what are you doing home early?
我找一张治牙的保险单，我牙疼得要命。
Oh,I need an insurance form. My tooth is killing me.
看啊我找到了什么了？
Look! Look what I've got!
是什么Ben。
What Ben?
看吧。
This.
是石头
Oh boy,a rock.
这不仅仅是块石头，
It's not just a rock,
而且是一块魔石。
it's a magic rock!
哦，那很好，宝贝。
Oh,that's nice honey.
对，是威尼卖给我的，才花了五美元。
Yeah! Vinnie Verbott sold it to me for only five Bucks!
哦，Ben，Ben，Ben！
Oh,Ben Ben Ben Ben.
什么？什么？什么？
What? What? What? What?
Ben，你过于相信人了。
Ben,honey,you're so trusting.
是件坏事吗？
That's a bad thing?
我不这样认为。
Not from where I sit.
Ben，你可要当心点。
Ben,you've gotta stop being an easy mark
你可别一连成为两个骗子的目标了
for every two bit con-man in the neighborhood.
别见怪，Mike。
No offense Mike.
妈妈，它可是块魔石，
But Mom,this is a magic rock.
它什么都能干。
It can do anything!
Ben，你想想，要是威尼真的有块什么魔石，
Ben,think. If Vinnie really had a magic rock,
怎么肯卖给你，才收五美元？
why would he sell it to you,for five Bucks?
他说喜欢我。
Said he liked me.
我从牙医那回来
Well as soon as I get back from the Dentists,
就打电话给史巴特太太，把钱退给你。
I'm calling Mrs. Verbotts and getting your money back.
我那该死的保险单哪去了？
Where is that stupid form?
让妈妈找到该死的保险单，
Let Mom find her stupid form,
让妈妈找到该死的保险单。
let Mom find her stupid form...
喔弟弟！
Oh Brother.
Ben，别闹了，我的牙疼极了。
Ben! Please,I'm in pain here.
别让妈妈疼，别让妈妈疼……
Stop Mom's pain,stop Mom's pain.
Ben，行了！
Ben! Please!
好极了，在这呢。
Oh great! Oh here it is!
什么？
What?
是保险单。
The form.
我说了，我这块是魔石。
Like I said the rock is magic.
Ben，只是巧合。
Oh Ben,it's just a coincidence.
你牙感觉如何？
How's your tooth?
我的牙……好了！？
Well it's...fine.
它要真是魔石我就是大猩猩！
If that rock's magic,I'm a gorilla.
这愿意可以满足。
That can be arranged.
我都不相信
No,I couldn't believe it.
连一个蛀洞都没有。
Not one cavity.
X光检查我每颗牙
The x-rays showed nothing.
都很健康。
My tooth is in perfect condition.
那当然了。
Of course!
Ben，你就别再吹你那块魔石了。
Ben,I think we've heard quite enough about magic rocks.
可这块石头是威尼从Mc姐妹那弄来的。
But Vinnie verbotts got the rock from Neil McGregor's sisters.
她们都是有名的女巫师。
Everybody knows they're witches!
可魔石并没有挽救她们
The magic rock didn't help their teeth,
落光的牙齿。
they don't have any.
我们都知道信仰的重要性，
We all know it's important to believe in something,
但信仰一些虚幻的东西只能会使你失望。
but believing in something that isn't real can only let you down.
可妈妈的牙疼治好了。
But it cured Mom's tooth ache.
我的牙是不疼了……
It did stop hurting.
你就别帮腔了。
Don't you start.
而且保险单粘在抽屉底下也被我找到了。
And I did find the insurance form stuck to the bottom of the drawer.
Maggie，保险单一向都粘在抽屉底，
Maggie,insurance forms are always stuck to the bottoms of drawers.
难道你忘了？
Where have you been?
爸爸，你不相信魔力，怎么解释世上的奇迹？
Dad,without magic,how do you explain the miracle of life,
宇宙的奥秘又怎么来解释？
the mystery and the wonder of the universe,
还有儿童的想象力？
the imagination of a child...?
还有牛顿的全部事业。
Wayne Noon's entire career!
你真的以为你这样说你就捡了个便宜货吗？
Must you take cheap shots at the man who brought us "danker shein"?
电视里的那些人不是只要寄钱就能帮你治病吗？
What about all those guys on TV who cure you if you send them money?
我钦佩这些人。
My heroes.
不过我认为Ben，
Look,the point is Ben,
如果世界上真有魔石的话
if there were any such thing as "magic rocks"
那可只能出现在加利福尼亚。
then the only place you could find them would be California.
事实上恐怕有不少人在寻找它们。
In fact,I'm sure the people out there are just tripping over them.
Ben，说不定你的魔石还能帮我们洗衣服。
Well Ben,maybe your magic rock can finish the laundry for me.
亲爱的！
Honey.
一位母亲的幻想。
A mother can dream.
我要去看书了。
Ah,I gotta hit the books!
Mike？你一看到书就会觉得胆战心惊。
Mike,books are those square paper things that frighten you.
说到书，Mike？
Speaking of books Mike...
哦，爸爸，我知道今晚要看书，
Ah Dad,I know it's a school night
但我得去和波拿确认我演讲稿的研究论点。
but I have to go to Boner's to check some research for my speech,ok?
去吧，Mike。
Sure Mike.
可爸爸，我……去吧？
But Dad I...sure?
但必须把你的房间整理好。
Yeah you can go just as soon as you clean up your room.
爸爸，我的房间属于我的天地。
D..Dad,I thought my room was my space.
那天地发臭了！
Your space smells.
全好了！
Perfect.
Mike？这就算收拾干净了？
Mike! You call that clean?
他怎么全知道！
How does he do that?
HI，Mike，给一美元我给你收拾。
Hey Mike! Clean your room for a Buck.
是你的了。谢谢你Ben。
Alright,you're on. Thanks Benny.
魔石，请你收拾Mike的房间，魔石，
Magic rock,clean Mike's room. Magic rock....
不，Ben，
No no no no no,Ben,
请你真的动手好吗？
you're gonna clean my room for real,ok?
它已经干净了。不信你看吧。
It's already clean. See for yourself.
还是把钱还给我吧。Ben，
Give me my Dollar. Ben,
你不能……
you can't...
Ben，Ben，我们谈谈！
Hey Ben,we gotta talk!
你别碰，
You can't have it!
不能给你，这是我的。
You can't touch it,it's mine.
给我吧，小Ben。
Ah,come on Benny!
我对你说过，我讨厌别人叫我小Ben！
Have I ever told you how much I hate being called Benny?
你说过多次，但我刚理解你的意思。
Yes,many times,and I'm just now getting the message.
很好。
Good.
你急着要去哪？
Look Ben,what's your hurry?
我得快走，
I gotta go.
我还有许多奇迹要表演呢。
I have many miracles to perform.
我想和你商量……
Ok,one quick thought here...
别过来。
Back!!
好吧好吧，别用魔石对着我。
Alright alright,don't point that thing at me!
他买了？
He bought it?
当然，肯定会。
Oh yeah,he sure did.
你这精神病医生可真会糊弄人。
Boy you psychiatrists sure know how to run a scam!
谢谢。
Thank you.
挺容易上钩的。鼻子让我们牵着了。
What an easy mark,he was ripe for the plucking!
Carol，咱们的目的是要让Mike尝尝受骗的滋味，
Carol,our purpose here is to teach Mike how it feels to be conned
把他骗你和Ben的那十块钱拿回来。
and to get back the ten Bucks that he took from you and Ben.
你说得很对。
You're right of course.
蠢货一个。
What a sucker!!
傻瓜一个。
Oh what a pigeon!!
真是太有意思了。
I love this!
要知道，咱们可以出售这种魔石，
Yes,well you know,we could sell those magic rocks
发它一大笔财。
and we could make a fortune.
你从报馆辞职，我也不干这活了，
Yeah,you could give up the paper,I could give up my practice,
我们可以全国转悠骗人钱财
we could all go from town to town fleecing and bilking people.
最后被捕，
Yeah then we could get arrested
然后我们就把我们的故事卖给好莱坞去拍电视剧：
and we could sell our story to Hollywood,TV movie of the week,
Seaver一家罪恶的生涯。
"The Seavers- A Life Of Crime".
让法朗·福斯特来扮演你，当然让张伯伦来扮演我。
Farah Fosset could play you,I'd be played by Richard Chamberlain of course.
电视剧第一集……
And in part one maybe...
Jason.
Jason，
干吗
Yes.
你故意这样说给我听。
You have a certain quality that gets on my nerves.
我只是认为你们对这玩意太热衷了。
I just think you guys are enjoying this a little too much.
摩玲·历瓦德他愿意拍吗？
Does Molly Ringwall do TV?
你就别说了。
Now stop it.
我只是想让Mike现在要得到他的教训
'Cause I'm sure right about now Mike is learning his lesson.
对，他就象一条小狗，到处跟着Ben。
Yeah...following Ben around like a little puppy.
哈哈哈。张伯伦演你
Ha ha ha Richard Chamberlain!!
你究竟愿意出多少钱？
Now how much were you offering again?
35，35美元，小Ben。
Thirty...five. Thirty five Dollars Benny!
你叫我什么？
What was that?
小飞侠Ben
Benjamin.
谢谢。50！
Better. Fifty.
可我没有五十美元。
Ben,I don't have fifty!
你有的。
Yes you do!
你生日时外公外婆给你的钱，
Your birthday money from Grandma and Grandpa,
藏在你衣柜的第二个抽屉的旅游杂志下面。
it's in your second dresser drawer under your National Geographics!
好吧，好吧，我去拿。
Ok. Ok. Alright.
那样我就会有点钱了。
Hhmmm. So I'd have the money but
可每天的垃圾还得我倒。
I'd still have to take the garbage out every night...
好吧，我来倒一个月垃圾。
Alright,I'll do the garbage for a month.
每天还要擦桌子。
And clear the table every night?
你这小子也太……
Why you little...
太可爱了。
terrific kid.
还不能让爸爸妈妈知道你付给我多少钱！
Of course Mom and Dad could never know how much you paid me.
那我就说是你送给我的。
No no no,I'll tell 'em that you gave it too me.
不，就说花十美元买的。
No. Tell 'em you paid me ten Bucks.
不多也不少。
No more no less.
随你的便吧，
Yeah fine whatever!
因为我明天的演讲课正需要魔石，
I just need some kind of magic for my speech class tomorrow.
成交了吧。
So it's a deal,right?
我还得考虑一下。
I'll sleep on it.
我的第一个魔法要把他变成蛇……
Well the first thing I'm gonna do is turn him into a snake...
不行，太迟了。
na I'm too late.
然后医生就洗手了，
Then the Doctor washes his hands,
房间用水冲洗，就这些。
they hose down the room,and that's it.
我关于婴儿出生的演讲到此结束。
Thisconcludes my speech on where babies come from.
有问题吗？
Well any questions?
不不，慢着，慢着。你讲得也太
No! No,that was extremely...
具体了。
thorough.
哦谢谢！
Oh,thanks.
不过我在想，如果想让
However,I can't help but wonder if it...if it really
演讲效果更好一点
wouldn't have been more effective
你可以用专用名称来称谓
if you had used the proper names for the..er..you know...
身体的某部分
parts of the body.
我就是这样做的啊。
Err,I did.
是吗？下去吧。波拿同学，
Yeah? You may sit. Er Mr. Stabone,
请你把你的实物模型也带下去。……
please would you...could...would you take your visual aids with you.
大家先休息一会，定定神。
Ohh,let's just take a moment here. Ok? And catch our breath.
演讲好极了，波拿。
Great speech Bones!
谢谢你，我三分之一的成绩就该靠它了。
Thanks a lot man,I knew a third of my grade depended on it.
好了，下一位该谁了？Mike Seaver。
Alright,well now let's see who's next...Mike Seaver!
看看这魔力吧！
Watch this Bone.
伟大的演讲！伟大的演讲！伟大的演讲！
Oh. Great speech great speech great speech great speech.
你的题目是什么？
What's your topic?
魔力。
Ah...magic!
魔力？我的上帝啊。
Magic! Thank goodness.
伟大的演讲！伟大的演讲！
Great speech great speech great speech...
你还没说呢？
Not yet it isn't.
魔力，石头，呃，魔力
Magic! Rock! Ah! Magic! Johnson!
Mike，我听不懂你在说什么。
Mike,I'm having a little trouble following this.
魔力。
Magic!
Mike，也许你的临产期也太长了点。
Mike,I think you've over done the pregnant pause.
你别发表意见，波拿同学。
Not a word Mr. Stabone!
不能失败，我不能失败。
Look,I can't fail,I can't fail!
你讲不讲？
You wanna bet?
Mike，你不演讲就回到你的座位上去！
Mike,either finish your speech or take a seat.
你究竟肯不肯帮我的忙？！
Look,are you gonna help me out here,or what?
我受骗了。
I've been conned!
好了，够了。
Ok,that's it.
对了，题目是骗人的勾当。
Right! That's it,con jobs!
你说什么？
I beg your pardon?
这就是演讲的真正题目
Yeah now that's the real title of my speech.
你们一定会非常欣赏的。
You're gonna love this Mrs. Skovanjario! Ok.
骗人的勾当，朋友还是敌人
Con jobs! Friend or foe?
每个人都可能上当，
You know anybody can be a victim.
你们信吗？
You don't believe me?
在座的各位都很聪明可我刚才已经使你们认为
You all look pretty intelligent,but I just made you believe that
我非常无能。哈，
I didn't know what I was doing up here!
你们全上当了。
So foolish!
妈妈。
Hi Mom!
宝贝。
Hi Honey.
Ben，你拿着什么？
Hey Ben,what you got there?
是一只棒球手套。
It's a catcher's mitt.
上面有巴马的签名。
A Buzzie Babone autographed model!
Ben，这个人打球不行。
Ben,Buzzie Babone's a bum!
根本接不住。
He couldn't catch a cold.
是买来的？
You bought that?
对。
Yeah!
哪来的钱？
Where'd you get the money?
哦……
Oh oh.
你该从Mike把你的
Ben,you were supposed to get your money
和Carol的钱要回来。
and Carol's money back from Mike.
我要了。
I did.
是十美元？
Ten Dollars?
对。
Yeah!
总共？
Total?
不是。
No.
Ben，是多少？
Ben,how much?
五十美元。
Fifty Bucks,
我想他该吸取教训了。
and I think he's learnt his lesson.
Ben,Ben!
Ben，Ben……
你给我站住，
Hold it!
你诈骗你哥哥了？！
You swindled your brother?
是咱们一伙。
We all did.
这是分成妈妈。爸爸，
Here's your cut Mom...Dad...
你的，Carol。
there you go Carol.
这是什么？
What's this?
Ben，我们只想给Mike一个教训，
Ben,we were trying to teach Mike a lesson,
不是向他骗五十美元。
not con him out of fifty Dollars.
五十美元？！呵呵，
Fifty Bucks. Ha ha,
真有你的！
what a chump!
哦，Jason，你的这个愚蠢的计划产生负作用了。
Jason,this idiotic scheme of yours has got way out of hand.
我只不过是想给他一个简单的精神上的教训。
Oh oh,well I was just trying to teach him a simple moral lesson.
没想到怎么会这样。
I don't know what went wrong.
波拿？请进。
Boner! Come in!
Mike呢？别把他藏起来！
Where's Mike? Don't try to hide him.
到底出什么事了？
What's your problem?
他完全利用了我的单纯！
He took advantage of my innocence.
你说什么？
Pardon me?
他把我的钱骗去了，
Mrs. Seaver,he like ripped me off.
把这块破石头卖给我，还说有魔力。
He sold me this stupid rock and told me it was magic.
不。
No!!
害得我滑板时冒险转弯
Yeah! I almost got killed trying to
差点把命送了。
take Dead Man's Curve on my skateboard.
这是真的？！
You didn't!
当然真的。我以为有人石头
I did! I figured,with this rock,
就可以去闯没人闯过的禁区了。
I could boldly go,where no man has gone before.
波拿，这根本不是什么魔石！
Boner,it's not a magic rock.
别开玩笑，我整整花了六十美元。
No kidding. I'm out of sixty Bucks too.
它升值了！
It's gone up!
Mike一回来就找他谈。
Look,we'll talk to Mike as soon as he gets home.
我也会。
So will I!
Jason，把波拿的钱还给他。
Jason let's get Boner his money back.
好吧，我们大家把钱凑起来吧。
Ok then,let's everybody give me their money back.
拿来
Come on give me that!
好，这是……
Right this is er...
Ben，你就连分成也要占我们的便宜？
Ben you've even cheated us on the split!
大部分工作都是我做的！
Hey,I did most of the work!
你原来还两头骗！
Why you little double crosser!
这算是迈阿密的罪恶。
What is this,Miami Vice?
好了，一共是五十美元，
Ok,this is...fifty Dollars
再加上一只巴马亲笔签名的手套。
and a genuine autographed Buzzie Babone mitt.
哗。
Hey!!!
是我最喜欢的运动员！
Cool it's my favourite baseball player!
谢谢。你们真是好人！
Oh thanks,you guys are ok.
这样吧，对Mike说我不想找他谈什么了。
Oh and tell Mike that I'm never speaking to him again.
还是明天我自己对他说吧。
Oh never mind I'll tell him when I see him tomorrow.
怎么样？
Well?
你看我多能干！
I am good!
哦，好极了！
Yes!
退了五十块，外加垒球手套一只。
Fifty Bucks and a new catcher's mitt.
手套你留着，算给你的奖品。
Alright! You can keep the mitt Bone,you earned it.
石头给我好不好？
Err,could I have the rock too?
干嘛？
What for?
我不知道，我想做纪念。
Oh I don't know...sentimental.
好，接着。
Yeah here.
Hey!!!
你别激动，它毫无用处。
Hey relax it's worthless.
是这样吗？
You think so huh?
什么？
What?
我拿这块石头去上化学课，
I had this rock in my Chemistry class.
林柏老师要我卖给它。
Mr. Rembelov offered to buy it from me.
什么？
What?
对。他是收藏家，
Yeah,it's a collectors.
他说这块象是电气石，
This is called "Termaline" or something like that.
非常少见。
Very rare.
而且他说愿意出两百美元。
He's gonna give me two hundred bucks for it!
波拿你太过分了！
Bone,this isn't fair.
你说，这多有劲！
I know,aint it great?
哦，你听我说，
Oh well fine!
可你想过没有？
But did it ever occur to you that
骗人的人最终自己也会倒霉。
when you con you somebody you always get hurt!
有人就是不接受教训。
Ah,some people never learn.
该上床睡觉了，孩子们。
Alright,that's lights out you guys!
Ben，Mike，得到了一个非常重要的教训。
Well I think that Mike and Ben have finally learnt their lesson.
但愿他们能这样。
Well I hope so.
对。他们知道说谎和
Yeah,well they've learnt that you can't lie to people,
滥用别人信任的人
you can't abuse their trust,
永远逃脱不了应受的惩罚。
you're not gonna get away with it.
行骗的人绝没有好下场。
People get what's coming to them in this world.
现在继续报导新闻，
Coming up on the news,
前总统尼克松今晚应邀出席
former President Richard Nixon is honored tonight
每个菜价值一千元的豪华筵席。
at a,thousand Dollar a plate,dinner.